twosigma.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy Policy | Two Sigma

Updated and Effective Date:  February 7, 2019

 ** _THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES TO OUR WEBSITES AND PLATFORMS._**

This Privacy Policy describes how Two Sigma Investments, LP and its affiliates (“Two Sigma”, “we”, “our” or “us”) treat personal information collected on www.twosigma.com where this Privacy Policy is located (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information Two Sigma collects offline, through email, or through other sites. This Privacy Policy also does not apply to websites or platforms where it is not posted and where a link to the Privacy Policy is not provided. It also may not apply to the practices of all Two Sigma subsidiaries or other affiliates.  For example, this Privacy Policy does not apply to customers or consumers of Two Sigma financial services or products with respect to your use of such financial services or products.

 ** _WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM AND ABOUT YOU._**

 **We collect contact information**.  For example, we might collect your name, address, and email address when you register on our Site, sign up for our newsletters, or apply for a job.

 **We collect information you email, submit, or post.**  We collect information when you contact us using the email address provided on the Site. This may contain personal information about you.

 **We collect other information.**   We may also collect usage data on how you use our Site and how long you stay on the Site through the use of cookies or other commonly used technologies (e.g. web beacons). This may include information about your browser, device type, IP address, etc. and contain personal information about you.

 **Aggregate information.   **We collect statistical information about how users use the website, some of which is derived from personal information but is not itself personal information.

 ** _WE COLLECT INFORMATION IN DIFFERENT WAYS._**

 **We collect information directly from you.  ** For example, if you register with us, sign up for our newsletters, apply for a job, or send us an email via the Site.

 **We collect information from you passively.**  We use tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons to provide and support our Site and each of the uses outlined in this Privacy Policy. Learn more about these tools and how you can manage them, by visiting our Cookies Policy, [here](https://www.twosigma.com/legal-disclosure/cookies-policy/).

 **We may collect information about you from third parties.  ** For example, our business partners or vendors may give us personal information about you.  We may combine this information with information that you give us via the Site.

 **We may collect personal information as otherwise described at the time of collection on the Site.**

 ** _WE USE INFORMATION AS DISCLOSED AND DESCRIBED HERE._**

 **The provision of personal data by you may be necessary for the performance of any contractual relationship with you, or where we have a legitimate interest to carry out the following purposes:**

 **We use information about you to respond to your requests or questions.**   For example, we might use your information to contact you about employment opportunities or to process your application for a job.

 **We use information about you to improve our websites and the information we provide.**   We might use your personal information to deliver the Site and/or customize your experience with us. For example, we may use your personal information to improve the Site, our recruiting efforts and our other internal business purposes.

 **We use information for security and compliance purposes.**   We may use personal information to enforce our rights, for fraud prevention, to comply with applicable laws and regulations, or to protect our company, affiliates, our customers, or our websites, or a third-party website or platform.

 **We use personal information to inform you about Two Sigma.**   For example, we might send you information about Two Sigma and what we offer.  We might tell you about new features or updates. We may also use your personal information to send you information about career opportunities.

 **We use personal information to communicate with you about your account or our relationship.**   We may contact you about your use of our Site. We may contact you about your account or feedback.  We might also contact you about this Privacy Policy or the Site’s Terms of Use.

 **We may use your personal information as otherwise described or permitted by law** **, for any other purpose as described in this Privacy Policy, or as we may notify you.**

 ** _WE MAY SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES._**

 **We may share your personal information within the Two Sigma family of companies.**

 **We may use your personal information to respond to your requests or questions.**   For example, we might share your personal information with third parties in order to provide you with services requested by you or answer your questions.

 **We will share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.**   For example, we share personal information with our vendors (e.g., IT services providers and background checks vendors), partners and consultants. We may also share personal information with companies that operate our websites.

 **We will share personal information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.**   For example, we may share personal information to respond to a court order or subpoena.  We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests.  We might also share personal information when we are investigating potential fraud or if we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or otherwise necessary to protect our rights and property, or the rights, property or safety of others.

 **We may share personal information with any successor to all or part of our business.  ** For example, in the event of a merger, acquisition, divestiture, change of control, or liquidation of Two Sigma or part of its business (or in anticipation of such an event) we may share your personal information as part of that transaction.

 **We may share personal information for other reasons we may describe to you or as permitted by law.**

 ** _YOU HAVE CERTAIN CHOICES ABOUT OUR MARKETING TOOLS_**

 **You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.**   To stop receiving our promotional emails, simply use the opt-out or unsubscribe method provided in emails you receive from us.

 ** _RIGHTS FOR INDIVIDUALS IN THE EUROPEAN UNION_**

Individuals who are located in or residents of the European Union have certain data subject rights that may be subject to limitations and/or restrictions.

 **You have the right to access, rectify and, subject to our other legal obligations and business considerations, erase your personal information**. You also have the right to ask us to restrict the purpose or to object to the processing of your personal information as well as a right to data portability.

 **Please note that you have a right to object to processing of your personal data where that processing is carried out for our legitimate interest or for direct marketing.**

 **You may have the right to lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal information with your local data protection authority**.

If you wish to exercise any of your rights under this Privacy Policy, please send us your request via email to GDPR@twosigma.com.

For the purposes of EU data protection laws, we are the data controller of your personal information collected on the Site. This means that we are responsible for, and control the processing of, your personal information.  Our data protection representative for the EU in the UK is Two Sigma International Limited, which can be reached at GDPR@twosigma.com

 **Our Do Not Track Policy.   Some websites have “do not track” features that allow you to tell a website not to track you. These features are not all uniform. We do not currently respond to those signals.  If you block cookies, certain features on our Sites may not work.  **If you block or reject cookies, not all of the tracking described here will stop.

 ** _TWO SIGMA SITES AND CHILDREN_**

Our Sites are meant for adults.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 without permission from a parent or guardian.  If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us personal information, please contact us at the address below and mark your inquiries “Legal / COPPA Information Request.”  Parents and guardians may learn more about how to protect children’s privacy on-line [here](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).

 ** _WE USE STANDARD SECURITY MEASURES_**

The Internet is not 100% secure.  We cannot promise that your use of our Sites or software will be completely safe.  We encourage you to use caution when transmitting personal information over the Internet. We keep personal information for as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We also keep personal information as otherwise required by law or for internal compliance or record-keeping purposes.

 ** _WE STORE PERSONAL INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES_**

Personal information we collect may be transferred to and stored within the United States. Our Sites are subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you live outside of the United States, you understand and agree that we may transfer your personal information to the United States. You acknowledge that if you do not consent or would like to withdraw your consent to such transfer by contacting GDPR@twosigma.com, it will impact your ability to use our Sites.

 ** _WE MAY LINK TO OTHER WEBSITES OR HAVE THIRD PARTY SERVICES ON OUR SITES WE DON’T CONTROL_**

If you click on a link to a third party website, you will be taken to website(s) that we do not control.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of such third party website(s).  Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully before you submit any personal information to these third party website(s). We are not responsible for actions, omissions or practices of third party website(s).

 ** _reCAPTCHA_**

We use the reCAPTCHA service provided by Google Inc. (Google) to protect your submissions via internet submission forms on this site. This plugin checks if you are a person in order to prevent certain website functions from being (ab)used by spam bots (particularly comments). This plugin query includes the sending of the IP address and possibly other data required by Google for the Google reCAPTCHA service. For this purpose your input will be communicated to and used by Google. However, your IP address is previously truncated by Google within member states of the European Union or in other states which are party to the agreement on the European Economic Area and is, as such, anonymized. Only in exceptional cases is a full IP address transmitted to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of this service. The IP address provided by reCaptcha from your browser shall not be merged with any other data from Google.

This data collection is subject to the data protection regulations of Google (Google Inc.). For more information about Google’s privacy policy, please visit:[https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/  
​](https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/)  
By using the reCAPTCHA service, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

 ** _FEEL FREE TO CONTACT US IF YOU HAVE MORE QUESTIONS_**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or other privacy concerns, please contact us at:

Two Sigma Investments, LP

100 Avenue of the Americas

16th Floor

New York, NY 10013

Attn: Legal / Privacy Matters

 ** _We may update this Privacy Policy_**

From time to time we may change our privacy policies.  We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy as required by law by posting a notice on our Site prior to the change becoming effective. We will also post an updated copy on our Site.  Please check our Site periodically for updates.  You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the website after such changes have been first posted

© 2019 Two Sigma Investments, LP. All rights reserved.
